<resources>
    <string name="app_name">covidvax</string>
    <string name="home">Home</string>
    <string name="search">Search</string>
    <string name="data">Data</string>
    <string name="about">About</string>
    <string name="sputink_text">Sputnik V (Russian: Спутник V) or Gam-COVID-Vac (Russian: Гам-КОВИД-Вак) is an adenovirus viral vector vaccine for COVID-19 developed by the Gamaleya Research Institute of Epidemiology and Microbiology in Russia. It is the world\'s first registered combination vector vaccine for the prevention of COVID-19, having been registered on 11 August 2020 by the Russian Ministry of Health.</string>
    <string name="pfizer_text">In March 2020, as the scale of the COVID-19 pandemic became apparent, Pfizer partnered with BioNTech to study and develop COVID-19 mRNA vaccine candidates. Unlike many of its competitors, Pfizer took no initial research funds from the United States\' Operation Warp Speed vaccine development program, instead choosing to invest roughly $2 billion of its own funds.</string>
    <string name="moderna_text">The Moderna COVID‑19 vaccine (pINN: elasomeran), codenamed mRNA-1273 and sold under the brand name Spikevax, is a COVID-19 vaccine developed by Moderna, the United States National Institute of Allergy and Infectious Diseases (NIAID) and the Biomedical Advanced Research and Development Authority (BARDA)</string>
    <string name="johnson_text">The Janssen COVID-19 vaccine or Johnson - Johnson COVID-19 vaccine is a COVID-19 vaccine that was developed by Janssen Vaccines in Leiden, Netherlands, and its Belgian parent company Janssen Pharmaceuticals,[22] subsidiary of American company Johnson - Johnson.</string>
    <string name="why_we_vaccine">Without vaccines, we are at risk of serious illness and disability from diseases like measles, meningitis, pneumonia, tetanus and polio. Many of these diseases can be life-threatening. WHO estimates that childhood vaccines alone save over 4 million lives every year.\n\nAlthough some diseases may have become uncommon, the germs that cause them continue to circulate in some or all parts of the world. In today’s world, infectious diseases can easily cross borders, and infect anyone who is not protected\n\nTwo key reasons to get vaccinated are to protect ourselves and to protect those around us. Because not everyone can be vaccinated – including very young babies, those who are seriously ill or have certain allergies – they depend on others being vaccinated to ensure they are also safe from vaccine-preventable diseases.
    </string>
</resources>